Wonderful!
Wonderful! Wonderful!
That one's already—
Ah... That hurt.
This is pain.
It makes me feel so alive.
Damn it...
This ain't funny.
Boss did say this bitch wouldn't
die easy, but still...
Do you dislike women such as me?
My wounds heal instantly,
meaning I can fight forever.
Do you feel there's any point
in fighting a woman like me?
Don't be dumb!
I'll just keep kickin' your ass,
no matter how many times you heal!
How truly wonderful...
And that's exactly why it's so sad.
Huh?
You sense the presence
of mabeasts, don't you?
And it appears someone else
is here besides your sister.
Isn't your concern dulling
the force of your attacks?
Hah! Like hell it is!
Not for Boss and his buddy!
No matter how many mabeasts show up,
he's just gonna laugh as
he sends 'em all flyin'!
Nope! Nope! Nope! Nope! Can't! No way!
Did letting Garfiel work
by himself backfire on us?
Don't sound so disheartened.
He might be out there right now,
screaming that we're all just fine!
Subaru, are you all right?
I guess it's time...
to make use of my unparalleled
knowledge of the modern world!
Bring it, you giant dog!
Taste the very spirit of science!
Dust explosion!
Er... huh?
Wait!
What did I tell you?!
Instead of doing weird stuff like that...
It's faster to do this!
I spent all my money on this!
It's the best oil out there!
Help yourself!
Spocha?!
Did that... kill it?
Damn, why didn't that work?
Not enough dust? Not enough firepower?
Oh, come on!
You used too much oil!
Well, I couldn't very well be stingy with it!
We can't put that out! We gotta run!
Otto!
The escape route in the office
should still be intact.
Get Rem out.
Right. I'll take good care of her.
Subaru?
Sorry, but I can't escape with you guys.
We have to split up.
But why?!
Sorry, Petra...
but there's one more left to save.
Beatrice-sama?
Once I bring her back, be her friend, okay?
I know you'll like her.
She's really fun to tease.
I'm counting on you guys!
If I burn to a crisp,
write on my gravestone that the
cause of death was Otto's oil.
I have no interest in walking
on that bed of nails.
Just come back alive, or I'll throttle you.
Subaru! Be careful!
Face the disaster that is yet to come.
I hate you. I hate you.
I hate you so much.
Since the day I met you,
I've hated you so much,
I can't bear it.
The disaster that is yet to come?
Does that mean this is the future?
You're a hero.
A hero is all you can be.
I...
Thanks for the help!
...you cannot even wield the
sword without it, thief?!
Subaru, I know you and
Emilia-neesama are both tired.
I'm sorry.
And yet I ended up just
weighing you down further...
My precious granddaughter has grown
into such a fine young lady, no?
I'm sorry.
If that's the case, I should've just been
wrapped up in that cave and left for dead!
I'm sorry I couldn't kill you.
Under no circumstances shall I be killed
by something as nonsensical as a curse!
There, you see? I win again.
To think someone I wanted to kill so
badly turned out to be a kind person.
If I bend my knee and lose my
sword, what is left for me?
What a nightmare.
What's so hard about sayin'
"I don't want to be alone"?
I'm gonna kill you just like
I promised, Natsuki Subaru!
I made the realization
that I have not walked alone
all this time, that is all.
I suppose we must shed every last drop
of blood in our bodies to atone.
You can just stand there running in place!
Magic, dragons, whatever stands
in my way, I'll destroy it!
Why won't the soul take hold?!
I believe praying to ask
for a favor is arrogant.
Prayer should be for seeking forgiveness.
Is this...
Echidna?
You will regret reaching out so readily
for a feast offered by a witch.
Good girl. Not turning
around is the right choice.
Wh-Who are you?
I'm, um... you know...
a witch so terrifying,
it'll make your hair stand on end!
Where's Echidna?
Well, she said she doesn't want to see you.
She must have had a terrible
time in the trial.
I guess so.
I hurt her really badly at the end of it.
How did the third trial look to you?
I saw lots of very sad worlds.
Was that really the future?
It was a possible one.
Of course, showing you
only unpleasant futures
was undoubtedly her way of bullying you.
Yeah. Echidna is definitely a mean girl.
You're content with just calling that "mean"?
How can you look so relaxed?
Huh?
Well, it's just weird.
You saw all those terrible futures, and yet...
But it's not guaranteed, right?
A future like that is possible,
but there's a chance it won't be like that.
As long as I know that, it's fine.
I can always fight it.
You don't think you'll break right away?
If I was alone, maybe.
But they won't let me be alone.
You're pretty strong.
That part of you is nothing like your mother.
Huh?! Are you saying you know my—
Yes, I know her well,
but I can't tell you more.
I promised I wouldn't.
I understand.
I won't ask you anything, then.
You're sure?
I know what it's like when
you can't say something,
rather than just not wanting to.
Besides...
My mother is Mother Fortuna.
I see.
I guess her evil plots
do good things sometimes.
Are you... crying?
I'm not crying!
I don't cry. I don't have
the right to cry now.
Nobody needs to have the right to—
What did I tell you? Not turning
around was the right choice.
You're a bad girl.
Go straight ahead,
and the trial will be over.
The barrier will be opened.
Hey, witch...
If you see Echidna, could you
tell her something for me?
What?
Next time we meet, let's have a tea party.
With you and the other witches, if possible.
Sure, I'll tell her.
If she doesn't want to come, I'll drag
her there by the scruff of her neck!
It's open...
Who is this?
This should be Echidna's grave...
Wow... This is the spell
generating the barrier?
It's so incredible, I have
no idea what it's doing.
I think... right here.
Yeah. It just ended.
I need to tell all the people
who are waiting for me.
Huh?!
What did I tell ya?
Mabeasts are a piece o' cake for the boss!
Don't you think you might
be overestimating him?
Come on, Rock Piggie! Get up already!
Maylie, I was hoping
you'd stay out of my way.
Elsa?!
Ugh! I had to go through so much
work because you rushed things!
Show a little remorse, would you?!
Garf!
This is where you were?
Big Sis?! Why the hell are you still here?!
Where's Boss and the kid?!
I have completed the mission entrusted to me.
You know why I remain here, do you not?
You sisters sure are givin' us hell!
Sisters?
Yes, we are sisters.
So it seems that, oddly enough,
both of our sibling duos are complete.
Can I assume this is a good
time for a fresh start?
Garf, do not worry about my—
Hah!
They say the Master Swordsman Reid laughed
as he drew his sword against a dragon!
That's an idiom used to
describe someone who's crazy.
Yep, I know!
That's my divine protection of earth spirits.
So long as my feet are on the ground,
everything I can see is
within my strike range!
Maylie, don't take a single step forward.
Big Sis, stay behind me and watch.
Garf! I will handle this one!
Rock Piggie!
Get crushed flat!
N-No...
No!
Elsa!
Do something!
What a slave-driver you are.
While your body becomes injured all over,
my wounds continue to heal themselves.
Are you starting to find it unfair?
Huh?
I ain't broken yet.
If I just keep killin' ya
until you die, you'll die.
Right, vampire?!
You know?
I always liked readin' books.
One of the witches was a
vampire a long time ago.
That witch is dead, so I can kill you, too.
If you swear you'll never do bad shit again,
I might just let ya off the hook.
You really are absolutely precious.
Gusteco, the land to the
north where I was born,
was a very, very cold place.
I was abandoned as a child.
I hurt people and stole
from them day after day.
I had no time to think about things
like living or being happy.
One day, during a blizzard,
I was stealing from a shop,
and its owner captured me.
Shut up! No one asked!
Since I was a girl, he took off both
my clothes and my underclothes...
But I just happened to find a shard of glass.
I didn't give it any thought.
I just drove it into his belly.
At that moment, even as I felt like
I might freeze in that blizzard,
I had a thought...
Blood and innards are so very warm.
If there is happiness in this world,
it is the warmth that
makes one forget the cold.
It was the first happiness I ever found.
You can't understand that, can you?
If ya know that, why the hell
did ya blather on about it?
Why, indeed...
It must be because you're so very endearing.
Sorry, but there's already a girl I like.
I ain't got time for some psycho bitch!
How cold.
But that's all right.
It's only your insides
that I have business with.
I will kill you, Elsa Granhiert.
My love for you will begin after
I kill you, Garfiel Tinzel.
Elsa!
What a thrill.
Love Me Down to My Blood and Guts
You all right?
Being too reckless is bad for you, y'know.
No need for concern.
Thanks to you, Great Spirit,
at least I'm able to fight.
I was correct to bring you outside.
I can't have that place—specifically,
that magic crystal—destroyed.
Of course, you should still
be able to achieve your goal.
Will you not attempt to do so?
You mean I should ask the
great spirit to stall you,
and use that opening?
You jest.
Even if I do that, my wish
will never be fulfilled.
That said, things will only
get worse if we continue.
You did strike terror in me,
but even a great spirit is not perfect.
I have to commend your meticulousness.
When did you put the spell on Lia?
Before heading for the Sanctuary.
Doctoring the contract
between you and Emilia-sama
while she was depressed after a
fight with Subaru-kun was simple.
You wanted Lia to stay discouraged?
Yes.
Restricting Subaru-kun's actions
took more effort than anything else.
He is the last key to the
unlocking of my dearest wish.
Unlike you, I am not merely testing him to
see if he is worthy of my dear daughter.
Don't get cocky, witch's disciple.
Am I correct in guessing that you now
remember what happened before your contract?
There are plenty of guesses you could make.
But...
I was remembering a man
who spoke a lot like you.
Is it so I'd remember that wound,
or perhaps a warning?
Either way, it's just backward-facing.
Backward-facing, indeed...
Yes, of course. I am forever
looking back upon the past.
For me, all the wonderful things
that ever happened were in the past.
All that exists now is a phony
standing atop a pile of corpses.
I'm not going to find
fault with what you are.
But...
What?
You're going to make Betty sad, Roswaal.
Ul Goa!
What a childish way to react
just because I hit the bull's-eye!
El Fu—
Too late.
Get back!
If you don't get up now, the next
one'll hit you, and you'll lose.
You make it sound so simple...
I could not be more disappointed, Ram.
I wanted your wish to come true.
I wanted you to exact justice for
your brethren and find happiness.
Ram?
After repeating it so many times,
after touching upon it so many times,
you still haven't realized
my true intentions.
I only wish I was just a demon
burning with hatred in her
wish to avenge her brethren.
If I were only out for revenge,
my heart would not hurt so.
But...
Roswaal-sama,
I...
love you.
Is something wrong?
Wrong?
Are you making fun of me? After all this?
I only said what I truly feel.
I know that can't be true!
You love me? How dare you say that?!
I am the one you hate!
I am the man who caused the
destruction of your homeland!
I know you hated me so much
that you wanted to kill me!
That was true at first, but not now.
What's true now is...
I love you.
Who would believe in such a cheap emotion?!
What of your revenge?
Did you not swear on the souls
of your brethren to achieve it?!
I do feel as if I've wronged my brethren.
But I cannot help that I love you.
I will prioritize my own feelings
over those of the dead.
Great Spirit!
You got it!
Next to my beloved daughter, it's girls
in love that I'll always side with!
Petty tricks!
Where are you looking?
It can't be...
Surprise! I just got bigger, that's all!
Wh-What...
That's—
As far as I'm concerned,
this is the root of all evil.
Now, at last...